{
    "questionnaires" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "title" : "Question Bank - 1",
            "questions" : 6
        },
        {
            "id" : 2,
            "title" : "Question Bank - 2",
            "questions" : 5
        }
    ],
    "questions" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "questionbank" : [
                {
                    "Question" : "A/An __________ assessment is one which measures what it is intended to measure",
                    "Option1" : "Valid",
                    "Option2" : "Unvalid",
                    "Option3" : "Reliable",
                    "Option4" : "Unreliable",
                    "Answer" : 1
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "The use of technology to enhance learning process is called __________ in education.",
                    "Option1" : "IT",
                    "Option2" : "ICT",
                    "Option3" : "Information Technology",
                    "Option4" : "Communication Technology",
                    "Answer" : 2
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "The philosopher who worked in mathematical and scientific didactics was?",
                    "Option1" : "Jean Piaget",
                    "Option2" : "John Dewey",
                    "Option3" : "Martin Wagenschein",
                    "Option4" : "Lev Vygotsky",
                    "Answer" : 3
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "According to John Dewey, the teacher should guide students the way of the knowledge as a __________ in learning process.",
                    "Option1" : "facilitator",
                    "Option2" : "guider",
                    "Option3" : "philosopher",
                    "Option4" : "partner",
                    "Answer" : 4
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "The primary aim of educational psychology is",
                    "Option1" : "To contribute to an understanding of sound educational practices.",
                    "Option2" : "To provide the academic background essential for effective teaching.",
                    "Option3" : "To provide a theoretical framework for educational research.",
                    "Option4" : "To provide the teacher with a greater appreciation of his role in the education of the child.",
                    "Answer" : 1
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "According to Psychology, all education is",
                    "Option1" : "Deliberate",
                    "Option2" : "Functional",
                    "Option3" : "Purposive",
                    "Option4" : "Self -education",
                    "Answer" : 4
                }                
            ]
        },
        {
            "id" : 2,
            "questionbank" : [
                {
                    "Question" : "The best definition of Educational Psychology is a study of teaching and learning” has been given by",
                    "Option1" : "W. Kolesnik",
                    "Option2" : "James Ross",
                    "Option3" : "Charles E. Skinner",
                    "Option4" : "N.L. Munn",
                    "Answer" : 3
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "Curriculum is",
                    "Option1" : "Course",
                    "Option2" : "syllabus",
                    "Option3" : "Co-curricular Activities",
                    "Option4" : "Over all activities of an institution",
                    "Answer" : 4
                },
                {
                    "Question" : "A development perspective involves concern with changes occurring over time in–",
                    "Option1" : "Form",
                    "Option2" : "Rate",
                    "Option3" : "Sequence",
                    "Option4" : "All of these",
                    "Answer" : 4
                },
                {
                    "Question" : " Which one of theories of intelligence advocates the presence of general intelligence 'g' and specific intelligence's' ?",
                    "Option1" : "Anarchic theory",
                    "Option2" : "Guilford's theory of intellect",
                    "Option3" : "Spearman's two factor theory",
                    "Option4" : "Vernon's hierarchical theory",
                    "Answer" : 3
                }
            ] 
        }
    ]
}